We discussed in the previous post when the stock
was trading around 820. Till now
we had given you 900. So today we are going to
update that the targets have been met there
and further rally seems to be divided and there are
no signs of reversal here yet. The
stock of JVM Auto has gone
completely into the blue style zone and
I think if the
momentum in it is seen even a little bit and if it continues, then
you will see it around 70. So those who have a shop should
increase their position by closing it. Right now,
I think you should keep it at 920.
Continue on JPM Auto
position was
also given to you by Rahul and
all our viewers
who must have taken the spread must have made huge profits. Targets were from 820 to
900 and today the counter is
moving around 940.